Oneida Community Collection
Oneida Community Collection
- Manuscripts and personal papers
  - Lord, John, 1874 (Box 64)
    'Colloquies with spirits' (12 p.)
  - Macknet, Carrie A., 1870-1902; undated (Box 64)
    1870 F 15 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1872 Ap 17 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Je 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1873 S 17 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1874 Ap 14 to Harriet Matthews
    1902 Ag 21 to Portia Underhill
    S 5 to Portia Underhill
    undated Thurs to Mary Louise Prindle
    [no year] My 6 to Mary Louise Prindle
    [no year] Ag 25 to Mary Louise Prindle
    undated Sun. to Mary Louise Prindle
  - Mallory, Gibson, 1851; undated (Box 64)
    1851 D 5 to Marcus L. Worden and Baker
    undated to Marcus L. Worden et. al. in John R. Miller file (D 1, 1851)
  - Mallory, Sarah, 1873; 1874 (Box 64)
    1873 D 30 to Harriet Matthews
    1874 F 23 to Harriet Matthews
  - Marks Family, 1885-1909 (Box 64)
    File of 37 letters to William A. Hinds, with undated fragments at end
  - Matthews, Harriet, 1847-1877; undated (Box 64)
    v.d. 8 letters to Charles Olds
    1847 Ja 1 to Harriet Matthews from E.H. Matthews
    [no year] Ap 23 to Harriet N. Olds
    1864-1877 File of letters to Harriet N. Olds, with undated letters at end
    1855-1857 Diary (typescript)
  - Mears, John W., 1873-1880 (Box 64)
    File of 40 incoming letters (copies; originals in New-York Historical Society)
  - Miller, Charlotte A. (Noyes), 1847-1872; undated; See also Sketchbook in Kinsley, Jessie: Writings (Box 64)
    1849 Je 11 to Marcus L. Worden
    1854 Ag 4 to Marcus L. Worden
    1865 Ny 6 to Beulah Hendee
    1867 Jl to Harriet N. Olds
    N 13 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1868 F 21 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1870 My 27 to James B. Herrick
    1872 Mr 26 to Beulah Hendee
    F 15 to Beulah Hendee
    [no year] F 29 to Tirzah C. Miller
    [no year] Jl 26 to Tirzah C. Miller
    undated Sun. to Tirzah C. Miller
    undated Mon. to Tirzah C. Miller
    undated 2 letters to Marcus L. Worden
    undated Thur to Tirzah C. Miller
    undated to Tirzah C. Miller & Helen
    [no year] Je 15 to Marcus L. Worden
    undated Sat. to Mary Louise Prindle
    [no year] My 25 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1866 Ap 15 Sketch entitled 'Light of the Lighthouse'
    1851 Sketch of Old Mansion House (photograph)
    undated 'The Brother's Pet' (pencil sketch + 2 copies)
    undated Portrait of John Humphrey Noyes -- see Noyes, John H.: Writings
    undated Photograph of sketch of Putney
  - Miller, George Noyes, 1862-1909; undated
    - Correspondence (outgoing) (Box 65)
      1862 N 7 to Edwin Burnham
      N 30 to Edwin Burnham
      D 10 to Edwin Burnham
      D 29 to Edwin Burnham
      1865 Jl 29 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ag 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
      N 1867 Ja 16 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Jl 3 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Jl 3 to Mary Louise Pindle
      Jl 7 to Nary Louise Prindle
      1869 Mr 29 to Nary Louise Prindle
      Ag 29 to Tirzah C. Miller
      N 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1870 Jl 4 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 12 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
      D 7 to Tirzah C. Miller
      D 7 to C.A. Miller
      1871 O 12 to Mary Louise Prindle
      1872 Ja 21 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ja 27 to Tirzah C. Miller
      F 16 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ap 9 to Tirzah C. Miller
      N 2 to Annie Kelly
      1875 Mr 1 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Mr 29 to Edwin Burnham
      Ap 10 to Edwin Burnham
      Ap 27 to Edwin Burnham (with Annie Kelly note to E.B.)
      1876 Ap 15 to William A. Hinds
      Jl 17 to Ida Kate Kelly
      1877 Ap 18 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ap 29 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1878 Ja 9 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Mr 24 to Tirzah C. Miller
      My 9 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 12 to James B. Herrick
      Je 26 to Alfred Barron
      Jl 18 to John Humphrey Noyes
      1879 Ja 5 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Ja 7 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Ja 8 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Ja 9 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Ja 10 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Ja 11 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Ja 13 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Ja 15 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Mr 2 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ap 20 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1880 Ja 16 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ap 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
      My 12 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 15 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 25 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 22 to Mary Louise Prindle -- with N.L. Prindle letter to Tirzah C. Miller
      N 6 to Tirzah C. Miller
      N 29 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1884 F 8 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 21 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Jl 13 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 18 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 20 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 24 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 25 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 29 to Tirzah C. Miller
      O 2 to Tirzah C. Miller
      O 3 to Tirzah C. Miller
      O 7 to Tirzah C. Miller
      O 27 to Tirzah C. Miller
      N 9 to [ ] Noyes
      N 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
      N 17 to Tirzah C. Miller
      N 17 to Tirzah C. Miller -- p. 2 dated N 15, 1884
      D 10 to Charlotte
      1885 Ap 28 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Je 8 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1887 Ja 5 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Jl 5 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Jl 5 to Mary Louise Prindle
      N 17 to James B. Herrick
      N 18 to Tirzah C. Miller
      N 21 to Tirzah C. Miller
      N 23 to Mr. Hamilton
      D 1 to Tirzah C. Miller
      D 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
      D 20 to Tirzah C. Miller
      D 28 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1888 Ja 29 to W.G. Kelly
      Ja 30 to Tirzah C. Miller
      F 1 to Mr. Ellis
      F 1 to Tirzah C. Miller
      F 4 to Tirzah C. Miller
      F 7 to Tirzah C. Miller
      F 9 to Tirzah C. Miller
      F 24 to Tirzah C. Miller
      F 26 to James B. Herrick -- in H.J. Seymour file (F 26, 1888 letter to J.B. Herrick)
      Mr 1 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Mr 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Mr 29 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Mr 31 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ny 15 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ag 22 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1889 N 15 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1896 Ap 3 to George Wallingford Noyes
      1903 F 13 to Pierrepont B. Noyes
      [no year] 5 12 to John Humphrey Noyes
      [no year] My 1 to Tirzah C. Miller
      [no year] D 28 to Tirzah C. Miller
      undated Thurs to Tirzah C. Miller
      [no year] Jl 25 to Tirzah C. Miller
    - Correspondence (incoming) (Box 65)
      Correspondence relating to The strike of a sex and Zugasassent's discovery
      Miscellaneous incoming, 1889-1903, undated
    - Artwork (Box 65)
      Pen-and-ink drawing of 'Village of Niagara Falls'
      Spoon sketches with draft of advertising copy
    - Writings (Box 65)
      "An episode"
      "Perfectionists"
      "Trip to East Aurora" and "Autobiographical sketch"
      Autobiographic sketch (1845-1904)"
      Untitled play (mss.)"
      "True account of the formation of the great breathing trust and why it changed its name"
      "Why Tom Jackson never married"
      "The wings of riches"
      "In Worcestershire" (corrected typescript)
      "Strike of a sex" Dramatic version by Edward W. Bryant
      The verses of a Community with notes" (1889)
      "Religion of Community""
      "Story of early O.C. life""
      "Daily life in the Community"
    - Published material (Box 65)
      The dodo
      The strike of a sex (1897
      "Miss Marrett's sister" in Young's magazine (Dec. 1899)
      "The dodo" in Youth's comDanion (Jl 8, 1909)
      Zugassent's discovery (prospectus)
      "The great" (10 copies)
      Obituary of G.N. Miller in Jewler's Circular (7/7/1904)
  - Miller, Helen Campbell, 1867-1932; undated (Box 66)
    1867 My 6 to Charlotte N. Leonard
    Je 30 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Ag 5 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1869 Ag 2 to Charlotte N. Leonard
    S 16 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1875 F 15 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1877 Mr 6 to James B. Herrick
    Ap 15 to James B. Herrick
    1879 5 12 to James B. Herrick
    S 21 to James B. Herrick
    O 23 to James B. Herrick
    O 24 to Tirzah C. Miller
    N 5 to Tirzah C. Miller(?)
    1880 Mr 27 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Mr 30 to Tirzah C. Miller
    My 5 to Tirzah C. Miller
    My 26 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Je 18 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Ag 4 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Ag 13 to Tirzah C. Miller
    S 7 to Tirzah C. Miller
    S 8 to Tirzah C. Miller
    S 10 to Tirzah C. Miller
    S 20 to James B. Herrick
    S 27 to James B. Herrick
    N 22 to Tirzah C. Miller
    D 15 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1882 Ja 26 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Jl 6 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Jl 26 to Tirzah C. Miller
    O 15 to Tirzah C. Miller
    O 23 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1883 Ja 18 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1884 Ja 6 to Tirzah C. Miller--in James B. Herrick file
    1887 Ja 4 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1932 Ja 30 'Memories of O.C.' (incorrectly dated 1943)
  - Miller, John R., 1851-1892 (Box 66)
    1851 D 1 to 'Dear Friends'--in Gibson Mallory file
    1852 Ap 27 to Marcus L. Worden
    Jl 16 to Marcus L. Worden
    Jl 19 to Marcus L. Worden
    1853 N 15 to Burnham
    1854 Ap 6 to 'Dear Friends'
  - Miller, Kenneth Hayes, 1892 (Box 66)
    File of 13 letters to Dorothy Barron
  - Miller, Otis, 1859-1878 (Box 66)
    1861-1878 File of 12 letters from Putney relatives
    1859-1860 Journal (70 leaves)
    1861-1862 Journal (141 leaves)
  - Miller, Tirzah C., 1867-1893; undated
    - Correspondence (Box 66)
      1867 My 2 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      My 20 to Mary Louise Prindle
      O 2 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      D 19 to Mary Louise Prindle
      1869 F 6 to George Washington Noyes
      F 26 to George Washington Noyes
      Mr 11 to George Washington Noyes
      Mr 28 to George Washington Noyes
      Jl 15 to George Washington Noyes
      S 2 to Mary Louise Prindle
      S 22 to George Washington Noyes--in George Washington Noyes file
      O 27 to Mary Louise Prindle
      N 7 to Mary Louise Prindle
      N 19 to George Washington Noyes
      1870 N 25 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Jl 14 to George Washington Noyes
      Ag 24 to Mary Louise Prindle
      N 8 to Mary Louise Prindle
      N 17 to Mary Louise Prindle
      1871 F 23 to Mary Louise Prindle
      1872 5 12 to Theodore R. Noyes
      O 11 to John Humphrey Noyes
      1875 Ja 14 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ja 14 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ja 27 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ja 29 to John Humphrey Noyes
      F 2 to John Humphrey Noyes
      F 3 to John Humphrey Noyes
      F 12 to Edwin Burnham
      Mr 28 to John Humphrey Noyes
      1876 Jl 12 to Mary Louise Prindle
      D 5 to Harriet H. Skinner
      1877 Ny 25 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ag 10 to John Humphrey Noyes (2 drafts)
      1878 Ap 2 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ap 4 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ap 21 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Je 1 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Je 2 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Je 3 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Je 13 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Je 20 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Jl 24 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ag 9 fragment
      S 8 to John Humphrey Noyes
      D 16 to John Humphrey Noyes
      1879 Ja 1 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Ja 31 to Mary Louise Prindle
      F 6 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Ap 25 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Je 1 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Je 7 to James B. Herrick
      Je 16 to James B. Herrick
      Je 17 to James B. Herrick
      O 15 to James B. Herrick
      O 18 to James B. Herrick
      1880 Ja 14 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Mr 19 to John Humphrey Noyes
      My 17 to Mary Louise Prindle
      My 31 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Je 20 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Je 26 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Jl 9 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Ag 23 to Mary Louise Prindle
      O 28 to Mary Louise Prindle
      N 8 to Theodore L. Pitt
      N 29 to Mary Louise Prindle
      1881 Ap 11 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ap 15 to Harriet H. Skinner
      Jl 9 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Jl 30 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ag 5 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ag 8 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ag 15 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ag 18 to John Humphrey Noyes
      S 7 to John Humphrey Noyes
      S 23 to John Humphrey Noyes
      O 7 to John Humphrey Noyes
      N 25 to John Humphrey Noyes
      1882 Ap 27 to John Humphrey Noyes
      My 4 to James B. Herrick
      My 15 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Jl 6 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ag 8 to J(?)
      S 15 to James B. Herrick
      1883 Ja 18 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Ja 22 to John Humphrey Noyes
      Jl 23 to John Humphrey Noyes
      1884 F 22 to Alfred Barron
      Jl 28 to Harriet H. Skinner
      Ag 11 to John Humphrey Noyes
      D 2 to James B. Herrick
      D 19 to James B. Herrick
      1885 Ny 6 to John Humphrey Noyes
      O 20 to Harriet H. Skinner
      1886 Mr 19 to James B. Herrick
      Ap 21 to Victor Noyes
      1887 O 2 to Harriet H. Skinner
      1888 F 6 to George [N. Miller?]
      F 13 to George [N. Miller?]
      F 28 to Mr. Hamilton
      Mr 6 to George [N. Miller?]
      1893 Ja 14 to Gertrude Noyes
      undated 7 letters to John Humphrey Noyes
      undated to Edward [P. Inslee?]
      undated to George Washington Noyes
      undated 3 misc. fragments
    - Writings (Box 66)
      1867-1880 Diary
      1867 N 17 "The transit of the trains"
      1877 D 25 "Parentage at Oneida" (From Boston Index)
      Other (misc. poetry, 1867 composition, etc.)
    - Legal papers (Box 66)
      Marriage license
      1876 5 2 Agreement between Tirzah C. Miller and Edward P. Inslee
      1878 Je 21 Covenant between John Humphrey Noyes and Tirzah C. Miller re: Edward P. Inslee (copy; original in John Humphrey Noyes file)
      1879 N 4 Marriage license of James B. Herrick and Tirzah C. Miller
  - Mills, William, 1864-1865 (Box 66)
    1864 D 23 to Gerrit Smith (copy; original in Syracuse University's Gerrit Smith Coll.)
    1865 Ja 2 to Gerrit Smith (copy; original in Syracuse University's Gerrit Smith Coll.)
  - Nash family, 1827-1945 (Box 66)
    Microfilm (35 mm.) of Evan Rupert Nash Collection at Stanford University (2 reels); guide to collection filed with film
  - Nash, Ellen, 1867-1879 (Box 66)
    1867 Jl 15 to Harriet N. Olds
    1879 Ap 3 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ap 5 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ap 6 to Mary Louise Prindle
    Ap 27 to Mary Louise Prindle
    My 4 to Mary Louise Prindle
    My 22 to Mary Louise Prindle
  - Nash, Olive, 1851? (Box 66)
    Sketchbook
  - Nash, Seymour W., 1867-1879 (Box 66)
    1867 Jl 14 to Harriet N. Olds
    1877 Ap 3 to Harriet Howard (copy; original in Amherst College Library)
    Je 21 to Harriet Howard (copy; original in Amherst College Library)
    1879 Mr 28 to Beulah Hendee
  - Newhouse, Eveliza, 1852; undated (Box 66)
    1852 O 12 to Marcus L. Worden
    N 21 to Marcus L. Worden
    undated 3 letters to Marcus L. Worden
    [no year] O 27 to Marcus L. Worden
    [no year] N 11 to Marcus L. Worden
    [no year] D 27 to Marcus L. Worden
  - Newhouse, Nilford J., 1876; 1878,; undated
    - Correspondence (Box 66)
      1876 Jl 17 to Harriet Matthews
      1878 Ny 16 to Mary Louise Prindle
    - Sketchbooks (photocopies - originals held by Oneida Community Mansion House) (Oversize 2)
  - Newhouse, Sewell (Box 66)
    Miscellaneous secondary material
  - Norton, Frederick, 1872; 1879 (Box 66)
    1872 Je 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
    Ag 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1879 My 22 to Mary Louise Prindle
  - Norton, John N., 1879 (Box 66)
    Marriage application, license, and certificate
  - Norton, Mrs. (Box 67)
    "Notes"
  - Noyes, Constance, 1871-1882 (Box 67)
    1871 My 11 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1880 Ap 8 to Tirzah C. Miller
    1882 Jl 5 to Tirzah C. Miller
  - Noyes, George Wallingford, 1879-1925 (Box 67)
    See also Archives (George Wallingford Noyes) (Boxes 1-3) for Oneida Community documents collected and transcribed by him
    - Correspondence
      1879 Ja 25 to Irene Campbell Noyes
      1880 Ag 29 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1884 Mr 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
      D 17 to Pierrepont B. Noyes
      1885 Ja 7 to 'Pip' [P.B.Noyes]
      Ja 15 to John Humphrey Noyes
      F 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
      188? to ?
      1894 O 3 to Stephen R. Leonard (II)
      1895 Ja 12 tp Irene Campbell Noyes
      Ja 27 to Dorothy Barron
      1896 Je 18 to Stephen R. Leonard (II)
      1904 Mr 7 to James B. Herrick
      N 9 James B. Herrick
      1923-1925 File of correspondence with William Findlay, Basco, Illinois
    - Writings (Box 67)
      'An experiment in home education' (1914) (copy)
  - Noyes, George Washington, 1847-1870; undated
    - Correspondence (Box 67)
      186- to James B. Herrick
      1864 Je 24 to Fidelia Burt
      1865 Mr 28 to Portia Underhill
      Ap 8 to Beulah Hendee
      My 1 to 'Dear Sister' [Portia Underhill?]
      1865 Ag 14 to Fidelia Burt
      Je 26 to 'Dear Sister' [Portia Underhill?]
      D 3 to Portia Underhill
      D 25 to Portia Underhill
      1866 Mr 18 to Portia Underhill
      My 21 to Portia Underhill
      Je 3 to Portia Underhill
      Jl 24 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 3 to James B. Herrick
      1867 Je 19 to John Humphrey Noyes
      O 14 to Portia Underhill
      D 1 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      1868 F 13 to Beulah Hendee
      Mr 3 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1869 Ja 5 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ja 15 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      F 3 to James B. Herrick
      Mr 14 to James B. Herrick
      My 10 to Tirzah C. Miller
      My 29 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Jl 14 to James B. Herrick
      Ag 6 to James B. Herrick
      S 13 to Harriet
      S 18 to Tirzah C. Miller (with her reply)
      N 2 to Tirzah C. Miller
      N 30 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1870 F 3 to Alfred Barron
      Ap 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ap 27 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ny 12 to James B. Herrick
      Jl 12 to Tirzah C. Miller
      undated Wed. to Tirzah C. Miller
    - Writings (Box 67)
      1867 'Roads & river sketches' - Scrapbook with sketches
  - Noyes, Gertrude, 1885 (Box 67)
    Stone Cottage diary (7 p.)
  - Noyes, Harriet A., 1847-188; undated
    - Correspondence (Box 67)
      1847 Je 28 to Lovett (copy; original in Vermont Historical Soc.?)
      1848 Ja 27 to Lovett (copy; original in Vermont Historical Soc.?)
      Je 11 to Lovett (copy; original in Vermont Hist. Soc.?)
      1852 F 24 to Marcus L. Worden--in Harriet N. Worden file
      Mr 27 to Marcus L. Worden
      Je 12 to Marcus L. Worden--in L. Burgess file
      1860 Mr 17 to Charlotte
      1862 Ja 1 to O.H. Miller
      1864 Jl 14 to Harriet N. Olds
      1865 Ja 10 to Beulah Hendee
      Ja 30 to Beulah Hendee
      Jl 12 to Charles Olds
      O 1 to Beulah Hendee
      1866 Ja 23 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 9 to Beulah Hendee
      1867 F 18 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Je 16 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      D 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1869 Ja 29 to James B. Herrick
      1870 Ag 23 to Tirzah C. Miller
      N 26 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      1873 Mr 15 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ap 16 to James B. Herrick
      Je 21 to Beulah Hendee
      Ag 4 to Beulah Hendee
      O 2 to Beulah Hendee
      1875 Ap 5 to Beulah Hendee
      Ap 20 to Beulah Hendee
      Ap 27 to Beulah Hendee
      My 29 to Beulah Hendee
      Ag 19 to Beulah Hendee
      S 23 to Beulah Hendee
      O 5 to Beulah Hendee
      N 29 to 'Friends'
      N 29 to Beulah Hendee
      D 23 to Beulah Hendee
      1876 F 21 to Beulah Hendee
      Mr 10 to Beulah Hendee
      Mr 27 to Beulah Hendee
      Ap 23 to Beulah Hendee
      Ap 29 to Beulah Hendee
      Ag 21 to Beulah Hendee
      O 11 to Alfred Barron
      O 19 to Beulah Hendee
      O 27 to Beulah Hendee
      1876 to Beulah Hendee
      1877 My 1 to Harriet N. Olds
      1878 Ny 5 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Je 13 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      Je 28 to Theodore R. Noyes--in T.R. Noyes file
      Je 29 to Nary Louise Prindle
      1879 Ja 28 to Tirzah C. Miller (1877?)
      Mr 9 to Mary Louise Prindle
      Jl 28 to Beulah Hendee
      Ag 12 to Beulah Hendee
      S 5 to Beulah Hendee
      S 24 to Beulah Hendee
      1880 D 3 to Humphrey Noyes
      1881 Mr to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ag 26 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1882 Ja 27 to Tirzah C. Miller
      F 26 to Beulah Hendee
      Ap 1 to Beulah Hendee
      Ap 30 to Tirzah C. Miller
      My 13 to Tirzah C. Miller
      My 17 to Tirzah C. Miller
      D 23 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1883 F 9 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      Mr 3 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      1884 Ja 19 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      Ap 6 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      My 10 to Harriet Matthews
      My 22 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      Jl 2 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      Jl 8 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      S 19 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      S 29 to Humphrey, Holton, George ("Dear Boys")
      O 14 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      O 17 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      N 27 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      D 4 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      1885 Ja 5 to Alfred Barron
      Ap 6 to Beulah Hendee
      1886 Ag 18 to Tirzah C. Miller
      5 29 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ap 28 to Dorothy Barron
      1887 Ja 9 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      Ja 10 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      Ja 18 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      F 27 to James B. Herrick
      Mr 17 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      Mr 18 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ap 5 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      Ag 5 to Dorthea
      Ag 30 to Beulah Barron
      Ag 31 to Tirzah C. Miller
      S 4 to Tirzah C. Miller (1881?)
      1888 F 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
      Ap 25 to Tirzah C. Miller
      1891 Je 28 to Beulah Hendee
      1893 F 8 to Maria [Barron?]
      [no year] Ja 23 to Beulah Hendee
      [no year] Mr 20 to Marcus L. Worden
      [no year] Ap 1 to Beulah Hendee
      [no year] Ap 12 to Mary Louise Prindle
      [no year] My 28 to Beulah Hendee
      [no year] My 19 to Tirzah C. Miller
      [no year] Je 20 to Tirzah C. Miller
      [no year] Jl 8 to Mary
      [no year] Jl 16 to Tirzah C. Miller
      [no year] Jl 21 to Tirzah C. Miller
      [no year] S 2 to Marcus L. Worden
      [no year] S 2 to Harriet N. Olds
      [no year] S 13 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      [no year] S 15 to Nary Louise Prindle
      [no year] N 14 to Tirzah C. Miller
      [no year] N 28 to Mary Louise Prindle
      [no year] D 3 to Mary Louise Prindle
      [no year] D 6 to Mary Louise Prindle
      [no year] D 24 to Charlotte N. Leonard
      undated Sat. to Mary Louise Prindle (3 letters)
      undated Sat. to Tirzah C. Miller
      undated Sun. to Beulah Hendee
      undated Mon. to Harriet N. Olds
      undated Mon. to James B. Herrick
      undated Tues. to Beulah Hendee
      undated Wed. to Beulah Hendee
      undated Thurs to Beulah Hendee
      undated Thurs to Harriet N. Olds (3 letters)
      undated Thurs to Mary Louise Prindle (3 letters)
      undated Thurs to Charlotte N. Leonard
      undated Fri. to Tirzah C. Miller
      undated 2 letters to Beulah Hendee
      undated 5 letters to Mary Louise Prindle
      undated 3 letters to Harriet N. Olds
      undated 5 letters to Tirzah C. Miller
      undated 1 letter to John Humphrey Noyes
      undated 1 letter to James B. Herrick
      undated 1 letter to Charlotte N. Leonard
    - Writings (Box 67)
      "History of M.A.H. [i.e. Mary Ann Holton]"
      "History of the printing business of the O.C." (mss.) 1872 Ny 31 Society to support & sustain Mother Noyes
      [Wallingford Community Krack Regiment of Girls]
      "Confession of faith and covenant of the Congregational Church in Westminster East Parish ..." (Bellows Falls, 1839) [with 4 p. mss. by Harriet A. Noyes]
      Biographical sketch from Holton genealogy (1975)
  - Noyes, Helen Campbell, 1867; undated (Box 67)
    1867 Jl 20 to Nary Louise Prindle
    1869 Mr 28 to Mary Louise Prindle
    1877 Jl 10 to Mrs. Gerrit Smith (copy; original in Syracuse University's Gerrit Smith Coll.)
    1878 Jl 9 to Mary Louise Prindle
    [no year] Mr 15 to Mary Louise Prindle
    [no year] D 11 to Mary Louise Prindle
  - Noyes, Holton Van Velzer, 1892 (Box 67)
    See also his A business history of Oneida Community Ltd. (Box 21)
    D 9 to Dorothy Barron